Guide to the Argus Archives Records
Argus Archives Records
- The Animals' Agenda, 1979-2002; 1979 2002; 50 linear feet
  - SPEAK: AA4 - program, 1995 (Box 2.086, Folder 25)
  - SPEAK: AA5 - leaflet, undated (Box 2.086, Folder 26)
  - SPEAK: AA5 - newsletter, 2000, undated (Box 2.086, Folder 27)
  - Speak out for Animals: AA1 - newspaper clipping, 1988 (Box 2.087, Folder 1)
  - Speciesism Awareness Project: AA1 - bulletin, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 2)
  - Speciesism Awareness Project: AA2 - newspaper, 1998 (Box 2.087, Folder 3)
  - Spiritual Activism for the Rights of Animals: AA1 - bulletin, 1997-1998 (Box 2.087, Folder 4)
  - The Sportsman's Guide: AA1 - catalogs, circa 1995 (Box 2.087, Folder 5)
  - Sproutletter: AA1 - newsletter, 1991 (Box 2.087, Folder 6)
  - St. Francis of Assisi Friends Association (SFAFA): AA1 - newsletters, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 7)
  - St. Louis Animal Rights Team (START): AA1 - newsletters, 1989-1993 (Box 2.087, Folder 8)
  - St. Petersburg Animal Rescue Organization (SPARO): AA1 - bulletin, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Animal Protection and Education Society (SAPES): AA1 - bulletin, 1994 (Box 2.087, Folder 10)
  - STAR Ferrets: AA1 - bulletins, 1997, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 11)
  - Stevens Swan Humane Society: AA1 - bulletin, 1995 (Box 2.087, Folder 12)
  - Stop Animal Exploitation Now (SAEN): AA1 - bulletins, 1996, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 13)
  - Stop Animal Exploitation Now (SAEN): AA2 - corrrespondence, 1996 (Box 2.087, Folder 14)
  - Stop Taking Our Pets (STOP): AA1 - bulletins, 1990-1994 (Box 2.087, Folder 15)
  - Stop Taking Our Pets (STOP): AA2 - newspaper clipping, 1988-1991 (Box 2.087, Folder 16)
  - Stop Taking Our Pets (STOP): AA3 - correspondence, 1995 (Box 2.087, Folder 17)
  - Stop the Overpopulation of Pets, Inc., Mansfield, Ohio (STOP): AA1 - newsletter, 1991 (Box 2.087, Folder 18)
  - Student Abolitionists League: AA1 - guide to materials in video library, 1996 (Box 2.087, Folder 19)
  - Student Action Corps for Animals (SACA): AA1 - newsletters, 1988-1991, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 20)
  - Student Animal Welfare Group (SAWG): AA1 - bulletin, 1989 (Box 2.087, Folder 21)
  - Student Coalition for Animal Rights (SCAR): AA1 - newspaper clippings, 1990, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 22)
  - Student Environmental Action Committee (SEAC): AA1 - correspondence, 1995 (Box 2.087, Folder 23)
  - Student Environmental Action Committee (SEAC): AA2 - bulletins, 1995 (Box 2.087, Folder 24)
  - Student Environmental Action Committee (SEAC): AA3 - newspaper clipping, 1991 (Box 2.087, Folder 25)
  - Students for Animal Liberation, Berkeley, California: AA1 - newspaper clippings, 1988 (Box 2.087, Folder 26)
  - Students for Animal Liberation, Berkeley, California: AA2 - advertisement, 1988 (Box 2.087, Folder 27)
  - Students for Animal Rights, Seattle, Washington (SFAR): AA1 - leaflet, 1981 (Box 2.087, Folder 28)
  - Students for Animal Rights, Seattle, Washington (SFAR): AA2 - newspaper clipping, 1988 (Box 2.087, Folder 29)
  - Students for Animals, Washington, D.C.: AA1 - leaflets, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 30)
  - Student Organization for Animal Rights (SOAR): AA1 - report, 1995 (Box 2.087, Folder 31)
  - Student Organization for Animal Rights (SOAR): AA2 - published article, 1997-1999 (Box 2.087, Folder 32)
  - Students United Protesting Research on Sentient Subjects: AA1 - pamphlets, 1987, 1993, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 33)
  - Students United Protesting Research on Sentient Subjects: AA2 - booklets, 1993, 1997 (Box 2.087, Folder 34)
  - Students United Protesting Research on Sentient Subjects: AA3 - bulletins, 1991-1999, undated (Box 2.087, Folder 35)
  - Students United Protesting Research on Sentient Subjects: AA4 - newspaper clippings, 1987-1988, 1993 (Box 2.088, Folder 1)
  - Students United Protesting Research on Sentient Subjects: AA5 - advertisements, 1991-1996 (Box 2.088, Folder 2)
  - Students United Protesting Research on Sentient Subjects: AA6 - correspondence, 1991 (Box 2.088, Folder 3)
  - Suara Sam (Sahabat Alam Malaysia): AA1 - newspaper, 1989 (Box 2.088, Folder 4)
  - Swedish Society Against Painful Experiments on Animals (SSAPEA): AA1 - correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 2.088, Folder 5)
  - Syracuse Peace Council: AA1 - newspapers, 1990-2000 (Box 2.088, Folder 6)
  - Tails-U-Win!: AA1 - brochure, 1997-1998 (Box 2.088, Folder 7)
  - Teaching Animal Awareness in Legislation (TAAIL): AA1 - pamphlet, 1998 (Box 2.088, Folder 8)
  - Temple University Press: AA1 - catalog, 1999 (Box 2.088, Folder 9)
  - Tennessee Network for Animals (TNA): AA1 - newsletter, 1999 (Box 2.088, Folder 10)
  - Terra International, Washington, D.C.: AA1 - newsletters, 1986, 1988 (Box 2.088, Folder 11)
  - Terrazas Publications: AA1 - press release, 1995 (Box 2.088, Folder 12)
  - Texas Establishment for Animal Rights, Inc. (T.E.A.R.): AA1 - newsletter, 1998 (Box 2.088, Folder 13)
  - Texas Establishment for Animal Rights, Inc. (T.E.A.R.): AA2 - pamphlet, undated (Box 2.088, Folder 14)
  - Texas Exotic Feline Sanctuary: AA1 - newspaper clipping, 1998 (Box 2.088, Folder 15)
  - Texas Humane Information Network (THIN): AA1 - newsletters, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 2.088, Folder 16)
  - Texas Humane Legislation Network (THLN): AA2 - pamphlets, undated (Box 2.088, Folder 17)
  - Texas Snow Monkey Sanctuary: AA1 - newspaper clipping, 1999 (Box 2.088, Folder 18)
  - Theosophical Order of Service: AA1 - newsletter, 1998 (Box 2.088, Folder 19)
  - ThermoCare: AA1 - brochure, undated (Box 2.088, Folder 20)
  - Tibet Press Watch: AA1 - compilations of articles and newspaper clippings, 1990 (Box 2.088, Folder 21)
  - The Tide: AA1 - newsletter, 1991 (Box 2.088, Folder 22)
  - The Tides Foundation: AA1 - newsletters, 1990-1992 (Box 2.088, Folder 23)
  - Tidewater Animal Defense (TAD): AA1 - published articles, 1998 (Box 2.088, Folder 24)
  - The Tidings: AA1 - newsletter, 1993 (Box 2.088, Folder 25)
  - Tiger Haven: AA1 - bulletins, 1999, undated (Box 2.088, Folder 26)
  - Tisserand Aromatherapy: AA1 - advertisement, 1998 (Box 2.088, Folder 27)
  - Tony Stone Images: AA1 - catalog, 1994 (Box 2.088, Folder 28)
  - Toronto Humane Society (THS): publications, 1989-1992, undated (Box 2.089, Folder 1)
  - Toronto Humane Society (THS): AA2 - fact sheets, undated (Box 2.089, Folder 2)
  - Toronto Humane Society (THS): AA3 - printed matter, 1987-1989, undated (Box 2.089, Folder 3)
  - Toronto Vegetarian Association (TVA): AA1 - bulletins, 1996, undated (Box 2.089, Folder 4)
  - Tortoise Trust USA: AA1 - preliminary report, 1998 (Box 2.089, Folder 5)
  - Total Animal Liberation: AA1 - bulletins, 1989, 1992, undated (Box 2.089, Folder 6)
  - Trans-Species Unlimited, State College, Pennsylvania (TSU): AA1 - pamphlets, undated (Box 2.089, Folder 7)
  - Trans-Species Unlimited, State College, Pennsylvania (TSU): AA2 - newspaper clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 2.089, Folder 8)
  - Trans-Species Unlimited, State College, Pennsylvania (TSU): AA3 - bulletins, 1986-1992 (Box 2.089, Folder 9)
  - Trans-Species Unlimited, State College, Pennsylvania (TSU): AA4 - newsletters, 1982-1984 (Box 2.089, Folder 10)
  - Trans-Species Unlimited, State College, Pennsylvania (TSU): AA5 - legislation, 1984 (Box 2.089, Folder 11)
  - Trans-Species Unlimited, State College, Pennsylvania (TSU): AA6 - correspondence, 1992 (Box 2.089, Folder 12)
  - Tree House Animal Foundation: AA1 - newsletters, 1987-2000 (Box 2.089, Folder 13)
  - Tree House Animal Foundation: AA2 - bulletins, 1987, undated (Box 2.089, Folder 14)
  - Trilogy: AA1 - magazine, 1991 (Box 2.089, Folder 15)
  - The Trixie Foundation: AA1 - information kit, 1998-1999 (Box 2.089, Folder 16)
  - The True Nature Network, Inc., New York, New York (TTNN): AA1 - newsletters, 1993, 1995, undated (Box 2.089, Folder 17)
  - TTT Report, Glauburg, Germany: AA1 - magazine, 1997 (Box 2.089, Folder 18)
  - Tufts University: AA1 - bulletins, 1995-1997 (Box 2.09, Folder 1)
  - Tufts University: AA2 - report, 1996 (Box 2.09, Folder 2)
  - Tufts University: AA3 - draft of proceedings, 1994 (Box 2.09, Folder 3)
  - Tufts University: AA4 - transcript of proceedings, 1993 (Box 2.09, Folder 4)
  - Tufts University: AA5 - program, 1993, 1997 (Box 2.09, Folder 5)
  - Tufts University: AA6 - newsletter, 1992, undated (Box 2.09, Folder 6)
  - Tufts University: AA7 - brochure, 1994, undated (Box 2.09, Folder 7)
  - Two Dog Press: AA1 - information kit, 1998 (Box 2.09, Folder 8)
  - Uniao Internacional Protetora dos Animais: P1 - bulletin, 1978 (Box 2.09, Folder 9)
  - Unione Animalista: P1 - bulletin, 1993 (Box 2.09, Folder 10)
  - United Action for Animals (UAA): AA1 - pamphlets, 1970s, undated (Box 2.09, Folder 11)
  - United Action for Animals (UAA): AA2 - bulletins, 1978-1988, undated (Box 2.09, Folder 12)
  - United Action for Animals (UAA): AA3 - bulletins, circa 1974-1992, undated (Box 2.09, Folder 13)
  - United Action for Animals (UAA): AA4 - newsletters, 1989-1991, undated (Box 2.09, Folder 14)
  - United Action for Animals (UAA): AA5 - statement, undated (Box 2.091, Folder 1)
  - United Action for Animals (UAA): AA6 - reports, undated (Box 2.091, Folder 2)
  - United Activists for Animal Rights (UAAR): AA1 - newsletters, 1990 (Box 2.091, Folder 3)
  - United Animal Nations (UAN): AA1 - printed matter, 1987-2000, undated (Box 2.091, Folder 4)
  - United Earth (UE): AA1 - information kit, 1992 (Box 2.091, Folder 5)
  - United Farm Workers (UFW): AA1 - bulletin, 1999 (Box 2.091, Folder 6)
  - United Federation of Teachers Humane Education Committee, New York, New York: AA1 - bulletins, 1998-1999, undated (Box 2.091, Folder 7)
  - United Federation of Teachers Humane Education Committee, New York, New York: AA2 - bibliography, undated (Box 2.091, Folder 8)
  - United Humanitarians: AA1 - newsletters, 1982, 1991 (Box 2.091, Folder 9)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA1 - pamphlets, undated (Box 2.091, Folder 10)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA1 - newspaper clippings, 1991-1997 (Box 2.091, Folder 11)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA3 - fact sheets, 1991, 1998, undated (Box 2.091, Folder 12)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA4 - published articles, 1993-1999 (Box 2.091, Folder 13)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA5 - bulletins, 1991-1999 (Box 2.091, Folder 14)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA6 - correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 2.091, Folder 15)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA7 - speech, 1994 (Box 2.091, Folder 16)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA8 - booklets, 1992-1996 (Box 2.091, Folder 17)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA9 - report [folder empty], undated (Box 2.091, Folder 18)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA10 - information packet, 1991 (Box 2.091, Folder 19)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA11 - information packet, 1999 (Box 2.091, Folder 20)
  - United Poultry Concerns (UPC): AA12 - grant proposal, 1998 (Box 2.091, Folder 21)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA1 - correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 2.091, Folder 22)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA2 - pamphlets, 1987, 1990 (Box 2.091, Folder 23)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA3 - fact sheets, 1990-1991 (Box 2.091, Folder 24)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA4 - guide, 1988 (Box 2.091, Folder 25)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA5 - list of publications, circa 1991 (Box 2.091, Folder 26)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA6 - court order, 1994 (Box 2.091, Folder 27)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA7 - newspaper clippings, 1992-1997 (Box 2.091, Folder 28)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA8 - report, 1996 (Box 2.091, Folder 29)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA9 - report, 1995 (Box 2.092, Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA10 - legal decision, 1994 (Box 2.092, Folder 2)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA11 - reports, 1991, 1993, 1995 (Box 2.092, Folder 3)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA12 - list of licensed animal dealers, 1995 (Box 2.092, Folder 4)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA13 - bulletins, 1993-1994, undated (Box 2.092, Folder 5)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): AA14 - bulletins, 1992-1996, undated (Box 2.092, Folder 6)
  - United States Department of Congress (USDC): AA1 - report relating to branding of seals, 1993 (Box 2.092, Folder 7)
  - United States Department of Health and Human Services (USDHHS): AA1 - publication, 1985 (Box 2.092, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of the Interior (USDI): AA1 -, 1994-1995, 1999 (Box 2.092, Folder 9)
  - United States Environmental Directories: AA1 - bulletin, 1994 (Box 2.092, Folder 10)
  - United States Fish and Wildlife Service (USFWS): AA1 - statements, 1992-1994 (Box 2.092, Folder 11)
  - United States General Accounting Office, Washington, D.C. (USGAO): AA1 - reports and testimony, 1993, 1998 (Box 2.092, Folder 12)
  - United States Public Interest Research Group (US PIRG): AA1 - bulletins, 1988, undated (Box 2.092, Folder 13)
  - United States Public Interest Research Group (US PIRG): AA2 - newspaper clippings, 1988 (Box 2.092, Folder 14)
  - United States Public Interest Research Group (US PIRG): AA3 - published article, 1998 (Box 2.092, Folder 15)
  - University of Oregon School of Law: AA1 - programs, 1995, 1999-2000 (Box 2.092, Folder 16)
  - Utah Animal Rights Alliance: AA1 - bulletin, 1996 (Box 2.092, Folder 17)
  - Utah Wilderness Association: AA1 - bulletins, 1993-1996 (Box 2.092, Folder 18)
  - Utne Reader Books: AA1 - guide titled "Y2K Citizens Action Guide,", 1998 (Box 2.092, Folder 19)
  - Vancouver Humane Society (VHS): AA1 - newsletters, 1994-1999 (Box 2.093, Folder 1)
  - Vancouver Humane Society (VHS): AA2 - bulletins, 1989-1996 (Box 2.093, Folder 2)
  - Vegan Action: AA1 - newsletters, 1994-1998, undated (Box 2.093, Folder 3)
  - Vegan Action: AA2 - bulletins, 1994-1995, 1999 (Box 2.093, Folder 4)
  - Vegan Action: AA3 - pamphlets, undated (Box 2.093, Folder 5)
  - Vegan Delegation: AA1 - newsletter, undated (Box 2.093, Folder 6)
  - Vegan Foundation: AA1 - correspondence, 1997 (Box 2.093, Folder 7)
  - The Vegan Market: AA1 - catalog, circa 1994 (Box 2.093, Folder 8)
  - Vegan Outreach: AA1 - newsletters, 1996-1999 (Box 2.093, Folder 9)
  - Vegan Outreach: AA2 - pamphlets, 1996-1999 (Box 2.093, Folder 10)
  - The Vegan Society: AA1 - bulletins, 1994, 1998, undated (Box 2.093, Folder 11)
  - Vegan Standards and Certification Project, Brooklyn, New York (VSCP): AA1 - bulletin, 1997 (Box 2.093, Folder 12)
  - VEGANET: AA1 - bulletin, 1997 (Box 2.093, Folder 13)
  - Vegans International: AA1 - newsletter, 1993 (Box 2.093, Folder 14)
  - Vegetarian Association of America: AA1 - newsletter, undated (Box 2.093, Folder 15)
  - Vegetarian Events: AA1 - bulletin, 1989 (Box 2.093, Folder 16)
  - Vegetarian Events: AA2 - newspaper clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 2.093, Folder 17)
  - Vegetarian Inclined People (IVIP): AA1 - newspaper clipping, 1990 (Box 2.093, Folder 18)
  - Vegetarian Foundation (Stanford, California): AA1 - magazines, 1994-1997 (Box 2.093, Folder 19)
  - Vegetarian Foundation (Stanford, California): AA2 - correspondence, 1998 (Box 2.093, Folder 20)
  - Vegetarian Network of Austin: AA1 - bulletin, 1997 (Box 2.093, Folder 21)
  - Vegetarian Resource Group (VRG): AA1 - bulletins, 1994-2000 (Box 2.093, Folder 22)
  - Vegetarian Resource Group (VRG): AA2 - newsletters, 1995 (Box 2.093, Folder 23)
  - Vegetarian Resource Group (VRG): AA3 - catalogs, 1995-1999 (Box 2.093, Folder 24)
  - Vegetarian Resource Group (VRG): AA4 - pamphlets, undated (Box 2.094, Folder 1)
  - Vegetarian Resource Group (VRG): AA5 - coloring book [folder empty], undated (Box 2.094, Folder 2)
  - Vegetarian Resource Group (VRG): AA6 - published articles, 1995, 1997 (Box 2.094, Folder 3)
  - Vegetarian Resource Group (VRG): AA7 - guide to food ingredients, undated (Box 2.094, Folder 4)
  - Vegetarian Singles: AA1 - bulletins, 1995, 1999, undated (Box 2.094, Folder 5)
  - The Vegetarian Society: AA1 - newsletters, 1991, 1996, undated (Box 2.094, Folder 6)
  - The Vegetarian Society: AA2 - published articles, 1998, undated (Box 2.094, Folder 7)
  - The Vegetarian Society: AA3 - bulletins, 1994-1998, undated (Box 2.094, Folder 8)
  - The Vegetarian Society: AA4 - report, 1995 (Box 2.094, Folder 9)
  - Vegetarian Society of Colorado (VSC): AA1 - bulletins, 1987-1992, undated (Box 2.094, Folder 10)
  - Vegetarian Society of Colorado (VSC): AA2 - correspondence, 1989, 1990 (Box 2.094, Folder 11)
  - Vegetarian Society of D.C. (VSDC): AA1 - bulletins, 1988-1998 (Box 2.094, Folder 12)
  - Vegetarian Society of D.C. (VSDC): AA2 - news clippings, 1990-1994 (Box 2.094, Folder 13)
  - Vegetarian Society of D.C. (VSDC): AA3 - bylaws, undated (Box 2.094, Folder 14)
  - Vegetarian Society of D.C. (VSDC): AA4 - program, 1997 (Box 2.094, Folder 15)
  - Vegetarian Society of El Paso: AA1 - bulletins, 1995 (Box 2.094, Folder 16)
  - Vegetarian Society of El Paso: AA2 - newsletters, 1995-1998 (Box 2.094, Folder 17)
  - Vegetarian Society of Maryland: AA1 - newsletter, 1994 (Box 2.094, Folder 18)
  - Vegetarian Society of New Mexico (VSNM): AA1 - newsletter, 1997 (Box 2.094, Folder 19)
  - Vegetarian Society of Southern California (VSSC): AA1 - newsletters, 1988, 1993 (Box 2.094, Folder 20)
  - Vegetarian Society of Southern California (VSSC): AA1 - correspondence, 1991 (Box 2.094, Folder 21)
  - Vegetarian Society of Toledo: AA1 - newsletters, 1993 (Box 2.094, Folder 22)
  - Vegetarian Union of North America (VUNA): AA1 - bulletins, 1993-1997 (Box 2.094, Folder 23)
  - Vegetarians of Kansas City: AA1 - newsletter, 1996
  - VEGGIE: AA1 - newsletters, 1993-1996
  - Veggie Jacks: AA1 - brochure, undated (Box 2.094, Folder 26)
  - Vermont Vegetarian Society: AA1 - newsletter, 1991 (Box 2.094, Folder 27)
  - Vested Interest Campaign: AA1 - bulletin, 1999 (Box 2.094, Folder 28)
  - VetEquip: AA1 - brochure, circa 1998 (Box 2.094, Folder 29)
  - Vegetarians International Voice for Animals (VIVA!): AA1 - bulletins, circa 1998 (Box 2.094, Folder 30)
  - Vegetarians International Voice for Animals (VIVA!): AA2 - magazines, 1998-1999 (Box 2.094, Folder 31)
  - Vermont Law School: AA1 - bulletins, 1999 (Box 2.094, Folder 32)
  - Veterinary Centers of America (VCA): AA1 - magazine, 1999 (Box 2.094, Folder 33)
  - Vieques Humane Society and Animal Rescue: AA1 - bulletins, 1991-1998 (Box 2.094, Folder 34)
  - Virginians for Animal Rights: AA1 - newsletters, 1991-1992 (Box 2.094, Folder 35)
  - The VivaVegie Society: AA1 - newsletters, 1991-1999 (Box 2.095, Folder 1)
  - The VivaVegie Society: AA2 - pamphlets, 1992, 1996, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 2)
  - The VivaVegie Society: AA3 - leaflets, 1999, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 3)
  - The VivaVegie Society: AA4 - correspondence, 1997 (Box 2.095, Folder 4)
  - Vocalizations (Voices for Animals - VFA): AA1 - newsletters, 1991-1992 (Box 2.095, Folder 5)
  - Voice for All Animals: AA1 - newsletters, 1995-1997 (Box 2.095, Folder 6)
  - Voice for All Animals: AA2 - correspondence, 1994 (Box 2.095, Folder 7)
  - Voice of the Voiceless: AA1 - fact sheets, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 8)
  - Voices for Animals, Charlottesville, Virginia (VFA): AA1 - newsletters, 1989-1994 (Box 2.095, Folder 9)
  - Voices for Animals, Charlottesville, Virginia (VFA): AA2 - bulletins, 1987-1993, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 10)
  - Voices for Animals, Charlottesville, Virginia (VFA): AA3 - correspondence, 1989, 1990 (Box 2.095, Folder 11)
  - Voices for Animals, Tucson, Arizona: AA1 - bulletins, 1989-1997, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 12)
  - Voices for Animals, Tucson, Arizona: AA2 - newspaper clippings, 1988, 1992 (Box 2.095, Folder 13)
  - Voices for Animals, Tucson, Arizona: AA3 - advertisements, 1987, 1991 (Box 2.095, Folder 14)
  - Volunteer Services for Animals, Providence, Rhode Island, AA1 - newsletter, 1990 (Box 2.095, Folder 15)
  - Volunteers for Animal Welfare (VAW): AA1 - newsletter, 1993 (Box 2.095, Folder 16)
  - Volunteers for Animal Welfare (VAW): AA2 - fact sheets, 1990, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 17)
  - Volunteers for Animal Welfare (VAW): A3 - newspaper clipping, 1990 (Box 2.095, Folder 18)
  - Volunteers for Wildlife: AA1 - newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 2.095, Folder 19)
  - Vulture's Quill: AA1 - newsletters, 1991-1992 (Box 2.095, Folder 20)
  - VWR Scientific Products: AA1 - catalogs, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 21)
  - Waltham: AA1 - press releases, 1995-1996 (Box 2.095, Folder 22)
  - Waltham: AA2 - information kit, circa 1995 (Box 2.095, Folder 23)
  - WAO (World Animal Orphanage): AA1 - correspondence, 1996, 1998, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 24)
  - WAO (World Animal Orphanage): AA2 - pamphlets, 1999 (Box 2.095, Folder 25)
  - War Resisters League (WRL): AA1 - bulletin, 1995 (Box 2.095, Folder 26)
  - War Resisters League (WRL): AA2 - magazines, 1995-1998 (Box 2.095, Folder 27)
  - WARDS: AA1 - bulletins, 1995, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 28)
  - WARN, Vista, California (Workers for the Animal Rights Network): AA1 - bulletins, 1987-1988, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 29)
  - Warriors of the Rainbow, College Park, Maryland: AA1 - newsletters, 1988 (Box 2.095, Folder 30)
  - Washington Animal Rescue League: AA1 - newspaper clipping, 1999 (Box 2.095, Folder 31)
  - Washington Animal Rescue League, Washington, D.C. (WARL): AA1 - bulletin, 1997 (Box 2.095, Folder 32)
  - Washington Animal Rights Network, Washington, D.C. (WARN): AA1 - newsletter, 1988 (Box 2.095, Folder 33)
  - Washington Humane Society (WHS): AA1 - bulletins, 1995-1999 (Box 2.095, Folder 34)
  - Washington Humane Society (WHS): AA2 - pamphlets, undated (Box 2.095, Folder 35)
  - Watchdog: AA1 - newsletter, 1999 (Box 2.096, Folder 1)
  - Waterloo-Wellington Alliance for Animals, Waterloo, Ontario, Canada: AA1 - newsletter, 1995 (Box 2.096, Folder 2)
  - We Adopt Greyhounds, Inc., Hamden, Connecticut (WAG): AA1 - leaflet, 1993 (Box 2.096, Folder 3)
  - Wellington SPCA: AA1 - newsletters, 1996, 1998 (Box 2.096, Folder 4)
  - Wellspring Publishers: AA1 - magazine, 1995 (Box 2.096, Folder 5)
  - West Coast Environmental Law Research Foundation (WCELRF): AA1 - newsletters, 1991-1993 (Box 2.096, Folder 6)
  - Western Ancient Forest Campaign: AA1 - bulletins, 1993-1998 (Box 2.096, Folder 7)
  - Western Canada Wilderness Committee: AA1 - newsletters, 1991, undated (Box 2.096, Folder 8)
  - Western Environmental Law Center: AA1 - bulletins, 1995, undated (Box 2.096, Folder 9)
  - Western Humane and Environmental Educators' Association (WHEEA): AA1 - bulletins, 1994-2000 (Box 2.096, Folder 10)
  - Western Piedmont Humane Society, Taylorsville, North Carolina (WPHS): AA1 - bulletin, 1998 (Box 2.096, Folder 11)
  - Western Suburban Humane Society, Downers Grove, Illinois (WSHS): AA1 - bulletins, 1991, 2000, undated (Box 2.096, Folder 12)
  - Wetlands Preserve: AA1 - bulletin, undated (Box 2.096, Folder 13)
  - Whale and Dolphin Conservation Society (WDCS): AA1 - printed matter, 1994-1998, undated (Box 2.096, Folder 14)
  - Whale and Dolphin Conservation Society (WDCS): AA2 - brochure, undated (Box 2.096, Folder 15)
  - Whale and Dolphin Conservation Society (WDCS): AA3 - newspaper clippings, 1998 (Box 2.096, Folder 16)
  - Whale and Dolphin Conservation Society (WDCS): AA4 - magazines, 1995-2000 (Box 2.096, Folder 17)
  - Whisker's Friends: AA1 - bulletins, 1997 (Box 2.096, Folder 18)
  - Whiskers: AA1 - catalogs, 1994 (Box 2.096, Folder 19)
  - Whole Foods Project: AA1 - newsletters, 1995, 1999 (Box 2.096, Folder 20)
  - Who's Who of Animals: AA1 - bulletins, undated (Box 2.096, Folder 21)
  - WHY (World Hunger Year): AA1 - bulletins, 1983, undated (Box 2.096, Folder 22)
  - WHY (World Hunger Year): AA2 - magazines, 1996 (Box 2.096, Folder 23)